export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'How do you say \'apple\'?',
    answer_a: 'abril',
    answer_b: 'mañana',
    answer_c: 'manzana',
    answer_d: 'arriba',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '\'Tengo hambre\' means:',
    answer_a: 'I am a man',
    answer_b: 'I am hungry',
    answer_c: 'I like ham',
    answer_d: 'I am angry',
    correct_answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'How do you say \'up\' ?',
    answer_a: 'abril',
    answer_b: 'mañana',
    answer_c: 'manzana',
    answer_d: 'arriba',
    correct_answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '\'Hace sol\' means:',
    answer_a: 'It is sunny',
    answer_b: 'I like the Sun',
    answer_c: 'How stylish',
    answer_d: 'Soulful',
    correct_answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Which of the following does not mean \'Excuse me\'?',
    answer_a: 'Discúlpame',
    answer_b: 'Lo siento',
    answer_c: 'Perdón',
    answer_d: 'Con permiso',
    correct_answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Identify the false cognate',
    answer_a: 'embarazada',
    answer_b: 'fantástico',
    answer_c: 'familia',
    answer_d: 'civilización',
    correct_answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '\'uno, dos, tres, cuatro\'...what comes next?',
    answer_a: 'diez',
    answer_b: 'nueve',
    answer_c: 'cinco',
    answer_d: 'siete',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a greeting?',
    answer_a: '¡Bienvenida!',
    answer_b: '¡Hola!',
    answer_c: '¿Qué pasa?',
    answer_d: '¿Cómo está?',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'What does \'felicidad\' mean?',
    answer_a: 'laziness',
    answer_b: 'kindness',
    answer_c: 'craziness',
    answer_d: 'happiness',
    correct_answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'How do you say \'summer\'?',
    answer_a: 'primavera',
    answer_b: 'otoño',
    answer_c: 'verano',
    answer_d: 'invierno',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Translate \'We are reading.\' ',
    answer_a: 'Estamos recordando',
    answer_b: 'Nosotros estamos leyendo',
    answer_c: 'Vosotros leeís',
    answer_d: 'Recordamos',
    correct_answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'What is the verb for \'to fly\' ?',
    answer_a: 'denominar',
    answer_b: 'descubrir',
    answer_c: 'volar',
    answer_d: 'destruir',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'What is the verb for \'to sing\' ?',
    answer_a: 'denominar',
    answer_b: 'descubrir',
    answer_c: 'cantar',
    answer_d: 'encantar',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: ' \'Aquí\' translates to... ?',
    answer_a: 'There',
    answer_b: 'Far',
    answer_c: 'Near',
    answer_d: 'Here',
    correct_answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'What is \'la cafetería\' ?',
    answer_a: 'the café',
    answer_b: 'the coffee',
    answer_c: 'this café',
    answer_d: 'a coffee',
    correct_answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'Which is the color \'green\' ?',
    answer_a: 'naranja',
    answer_b: 'genial',
    answer_c: 'verde',
    answer_d: 'amarillo',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: ' \'___ se llama Andrés.\' Fill in the blank.',
    answer_a: 'Ellos',
    answer_b: 'Ella',
    answer_c: 'Él',
    answer_d: 'El',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'How do you say \'Goodnight\' ?',
    answer_a: 'Buenas noches',
    answer_b: 'Buenas tardes',
    answer_c: 'Buenos días',
    answer_d: 'Adiós',
    correct_answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: '\'Quiero viajar a Alemania\' translates to... ?',
    answer_a: 'I want to travel to England.',
    answer_b: 'I want to travel to Europe.',
    answer_c: 'I want to travel to Armenia.',
    answer_d: 'I want to travel to Germany.',
    correct_answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: ' \'Why are you late?\'  \'¿ ___ estás tarde?\' Fill in the blank.',
    answer_a: 'Porque',
    answer_b: 'Ahora',
    answer_c: 'Por qué',
    answer_d: 'Tú',
    correct_answer: 'c'
  }
]
